{
    "subject": "Henri-Georges_Clouzot",
    "predicate": "created",
    "object": "Le_Corbeau",
    "human_readable": "Henri-Georges Clouzot created the film Le Corbeau.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9422181844711304,
            "question": "What is the name of the film created by Henri-Georges Clouzot?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7512981295585632,
            "question": "Is Henri-Georges Clouzot a filmmaker?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7494682669639587,
            "question": "Who directed the film Le Corbeau?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6924932599067688,
            "question": "What other films has Henri-Georges Clouzot directed?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.47605979442596436,
            "question": "What is the plot of Le Corbeau?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.44342049956321716,
            "question": "Where was Le Corbeau filmed?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.43361446261405945,
            "question": "When was Le Corbeau released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.42385244369506836,
            "question": "What genre is Le Corbeau?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3658233880996704,
            "question": "What are some common themes explored in Le Corbeau?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3346644341945648,
            "question": "How did Le Corbeau perform critically and commercially?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Henri-Georges Clouzot created the film Le Corbeau.",
            "html": "yago_23823_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some common themes explored in Le Corbeau?",
            "html": "yago_23823_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What genre is Le Corbeau?",
            "html": "yago_23823_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=When was Le Corbeau released?",
            "html": "yago_23823_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_23823_112.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_23823_118.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_23823_121.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_23823_122.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_23823_140.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_23823_143.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_23823_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_23823_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_23823_88.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_23823_91.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "After analyzing the provided context information, I can confirm that:\n\n* The first file (17.txt) mentions that \"Le Corbeau\" is a film directed by Henri-Georges Clouzot.\n* Other files mention the same director and his association with the film.\n\nTherefore, the answer is:\n{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information about Henri-Georges Clouzot and his film \"Le Corbeau,\" confirming that he was indeed the creator of this work."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        }
    },
    "final_decision": "true",
    "actual_decision": "true",
    "analysis": {
        "error_category": "caafscd",
        "error_detail": "cdscsd",
        "category": "csdcs",
        "stratum": "fwefew",
        "topic": "wefw"
    }
}